<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>每日英语 on 愿我如星君如月，夜夜流光相皎洁！</title>
    <link>https://yuallon.github.io/tags/%E6%AF%8F%E6%97%A5%E8%8B%B1%E8%AF%AD/</link>
    <description>Recent content in 每日英语 on 愿我如星君如月，夜夜流光相皎洁！</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 02 Aug 2020 23:12:11 +0800</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://yuallon.github.io/tags/%E6%AF%8F%E6%97%A5%E8%8B%B1%E8%AF%AD/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>每日英语20200802</title>
      <link>https://yuallon.github.io/post/%E6%AF%8F%E6%97%A5%E8%8B%B1%E8%AF%AD%E5%AD%A6%E4%B9%A020200802/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 02 Aug 2020 23:12:11 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://yuallon.github.io/post/%E6%AF%8F%E6%97%A5%E8%8B%B1%E8%AF%AD%E5%AD%A6%E4%B9%A020200802/</guid>
      <description>Staying Safe During a Lightning Storm From VOA Learning English, this is the Health &amp;amp; Lifestyle Report. Lightning is one of the most powerful weather forces to hit Earth. These huge bolts of electricity that strike during storms can cause destruction and death. Lightning can heat the air around it to temperatures five times hotter than the surface of the sun. Lightning is very common. It is estimated that every</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>每日英语学习20200801</title>
      <link>https://yuallon.github.io/post/%E6%AF%8F%E6%97%A5%E8%8B%B1%E8%AF%AD%E5%AD%A6%E4%B9%A020200801/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 01 Aug 2020 20:08:56 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://yuallon.github.io/post/%E6%AF%8F%E6%97%A5%E8%8B%B1%E8%AF%AD%E5%AD%A6%E4%B9%A020200801/</guid>
      <description>The breakfast history of America Since the earliest days of the United States, Americans began their days by eating whatever was most easily availble. These foods often included breads, eggs or leftovers(复数表示剩余物，残羹剩饭；单数表示遗物，遗留) &amp;ndash; food left ove</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>每日英语学习20200730</title>
      <link>https://yuallon.github.io/post/%E6%AF%8F%E6%97%A5%E8%8B%B1%E8%AF%AD%E5%AD%A6%E4%B9%A020200730/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Jul 2020 22:32:09 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://yuallon.github.io/post/%E6%AF%8F%E6%97%A5%E8%8B%B1%E8%AF%AD%E5%AD%A6%E4%B9%A020200730/</guid>
      <description>When you feel depressed, you can hold a tree! To stay safe during the corovirus pandemic, we have had to sacrifice（牺牲） many things we enjoy, including physical contact with others. Gone are handshakes, kisses and hugs. Research has shown that humans need physical touch to stay mentally and physically healthy. Without it, many become lonely, sad and even</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Eleven Ways the Little Prince Prepared Us for Adulthood</title>
      <link>https://yuallon.github.io/post/eleven-ways-the-little-prince-prepared-us-for-adulthood/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 19 Jul 2020 23:05:30 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://yuallon.github.io/post/eleven-ways-the-little-prince-prepared-us-for-adulthood/</guid>
      <description>[Forward] How &amp;lsquo;The Little Prince&amp;rsquo; Prepped Us For Adulthood By Bustle To a child, the grown-up world can be perplexing. What is this &amp;ldquo;work&amp;rdquo; they always claim to have? Why do they refuse to run around in fields and find shapes in clouds? And why do they assume that children know nothing? Anyone who remembers her child self will probably remember being completely confused by this adult world that seemed</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Talk About Food</title>
      <link>https://yuallon.github.io/post/talk-about-food/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Jul 2020 22:34:59 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://yuallon.github.io/post/talk-about-food/</guid>
      <description>When we meet a foreigner or have a break in an international conference, what&amp;rsquo;s the best way to star conversation topics? According to research, food is one of the most common topics people talk about while on break. ###Why is talking about food such a great idea? People like food. Thinking about food, thinking about dessert or main dished. Food can bring people together. At work, we often have barbecues</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to Express Rain in English</title>
      <link>https://yuallon.github.io/post/how-to-express-rain-in-english/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 Jul 2020 17:07:40 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://yuallon.github.io/post/how-to-express-rain-in-english/</guid>
      <description>drizzle or sprink n. very little rain; stronger than mist, but less than a shower. v. rain lightly It&amp;rsquo;s drizzling now. When it drizzles in summer, hiking can be pleasant. shower n. a sudden rain thundershower/meteor shower 雷阵雨/流星雨 He is so afraid of thundershower. pour n. rain heavily dounpour 倾盆大雨 When it rains, it pours. /习语：祸不</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Going to the PHARMACY</title>
      <link>https://yuallon.github.io/post/going-to-the-pharmacy/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Jul 2020 22:30:43 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://yuallon.github.io/post/going-to-the-pharmacy/</guid>
      <description>If we go to a pharmacy, what should we pay attention to? A pharmacy is a place where you can get medication or medicine. Another word for pharmacy is drugstore. medicine/drugs prescription drugs: you need a doctor to say, &amp;ldquo;Take this&amp;rdquo; Over the counter drugs: you do not need a prescription people in pharmacy pharmacist: a person who work at the pharmacy. they are an expert in medication. clerk/ pharmacy</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to Cancle Plans in English</title>
      <link>https://yuallon.github.io/post/how-to-cancle-plans-in-english/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Jul 2020 19:55:02 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://yuallon.github.io/post/how-to-cancle-plans-in-english/</guid>
      <description>Sometimes, we have to cancel our plans with someone due to something unexpected. Maybe we are sick. Maybe we have to go to work. When we have to cancel plans, it&amp;rsquo;s important to know how to do it in a polite that does not hurt the feelings or offend the feelings of other people. ###Here list 5 easy steps First, ask &amp;ldquo;How are you doing?&amp;quot;,when you meet your friend or</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Smartphone generation Should Wait for the Elderly to Catch Up</title>
      <link>https://yuallon.github.io/post/smartphone-generation-should-wait-for-the-elderly-to-catch-up/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Jul 2020 22:01:44 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://yuallon.github.io/post/smartphone-generation-should-wait-for-the-elderly-to-catch-up/</guid>
      <description>The technology development and aging. This is a good topic. According to the National Bureau of Statistics, the number of people aged 60 and above was 253.88 million in 2019, that is 18.1 percent of China&amp;rsquo;s population. But only 23 percent of the senior citizens were able to access the internet. With the advent of online payment, which greatly makes our lives easier. Wherever we go, we can make payment</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>War Poverty and Pandemic</title>
      <link>https://yuallon.github.io/post/warpovertypandemic/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Jun 2020 16:46:08 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://yuallon.github.io/post/warpovertypandemic/</guid>
      <description>Today, I want to share a cartoon drawing a family flee their home owing to the war and meet the pandemic. The story is compact but make me ponder. I will slice the picture into many parts and translate the words into Chinese. War, Poverty and Pandemic Families flee their homes to save their lives but they can&amp;rsquo;t outrun the coronavirus. By Heather Murdock and Brian Williamson | VOA News</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>每日英语06 22 2020</title>
      <link>https://yuallon.github.io/post/%E6%AF%8F%E6%97%A5%E8%8B%B1%E8%AF%AD06-22-2020/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Jun 2020 23:29:21 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://yuallon.github.io/post/%E6%AF%8F%E6%97%A5%E8%8B%B1%E8%AF%AD06-22-2020/</guid>
      <description>Seven steps can stop bad information We want to help our family and friends when we read some information going viral on the internet, especially COVID-19. Here are some advice to help us avoid the fishy site. 1 Stop and think One thing you can do to halt misinformation is to simply stop and think. If you have any doubts, pause, and check it out further. 2 Check your source</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>