<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>英文 on 愿我如星君如月，夜夜流光相皎洁！</title>
    <link>https://yuallon.github.io/categories/%E8%8B%B1%E6%96%87/</link>
    <description>Recent content in 英文 on 愿我如星君如月，夜夜流光相皎洁！</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 21 Aug 2020 22:27:49 +0800</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://yuallon.github.io/categories/%E8%8B%B1%E6%96%87/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>每日英语学习20200821</title>
      <link>https://yuallon.github.io/post/%E6%AF%8F%E6%97%A5%E8%8B%B1%E8%AF%AD%E5%AD%A6%E4%B9%A020200821/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 21 Aug 2020 22:27:49 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://yuallon.github.io/post/%E6%AF%8F%E6%97%A5%E8%8B%B1%E8%AF%AD%E5%AD%A6%E4%B9%A020200821/</guid>
      <description>Words consternation [U] a feeling of shock or worry attendance [U] being present somewhere [C, U] the number of people who go to or are present at a place gallery [C] a building or room where works of art are shown to the public chore [C] a job that is not interesting but that you must do houseworl chores ripe [adj] (used about ftuit, grain, etc) ready to be picked</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>每日英语学习20200820</title>
      <link>https://yuallon.github.io/post/%E6%AF%8F%E6%97%A5%E8%8B%B1%E8%AF%AD%E5%AD%A6%E4%B9%A020200820/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Aug 2020 20:18:32 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://yuallon.github.io/post/%E6%AF%8F%E6%97%A5%E8%8B%B1%E8%AF%AD%E5%AD%A6%E4%B9%A020200820/</guid>
      <description>Words inhabitant [C, usually pl] a person or animal that live in a place acquisition [U] the act of obtaining or buying sth We study for the acquisition of knowledge. [C] something that you have obtained or bought lengthen [v] to become longer or to make sth longer colloquial [adj] (used about words, phrases, etc) used in spoken English conversation, not in formal situations bulb [C] the glass part of</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>每日英语学习20200819</title>
      <link>https://yuallon.github.io/post/%E6%AF%8F%E6%97%A5%E8%8B%B1%E8%AF%AD%E5%AD%A6%E4%B9%A020200819/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Aug 2020 16:04:28 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://yuallon.github.io/post/%E6%AF%8F%E6%97%A5%E8%8B%B1%E8%AF%AD%E5%AD%A6%E4%B9%A020200819/</guid>
      <description>Words construction [U] the act or method of building or making sth A new bridge is under construction. literary [adj] of or concerned with literature. astonish [vt] to surprise sb very much definitive [adj] in a form of that cannot be changed or that cannot be improved inert [adj] not able to move or act [adj] (used about chemical elements) that donot react with other chemicals patrol [v] to go</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>每日英语学习20200818</title>
      <link>https://yuallon.github.io/post/%E6%AF%8F%E6%97%A5%E8%8B%B1%E8%AF%AD%E5%AD%A6%E4%B9%A020200818/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Aug 2020 18:28:54 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://yuallon.github.io/post/%E6%AF%8F%E6%97%A5%E8%8B%B1%E8%AF%AD%E5%AD%A6%E4%B9%A020200818/</guid>
      <description>Words aesthetic [adj] concerned with beauty or art interaction [adj] (of two things) to have an effect on each other interaction between/with sth/sb Audience can have interaction with TV hosts through the Internet. refined [adj] (used about a substance) that has been made pure by having other substance taken out of it [adj] (used about a person) polite; having very good manners cassette [C] a small flat case with tape</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>每日英语学习20200817</title>
      <link>https://yuallon.github.io/post/%E6%AF%8F%E6%97%A5%E8%8B%B1%E8%AF%AD%E5%AD%A6%E4%B9%A020200817/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Aug 2020 22:31:08 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://yuallon.github.io/post/%E6%AF%8F%E6%97%A5%E8%8B%B1%E8%AF%AD%E5%AD%A6%E4%B9%A020200817/</guid>
      <description>Words dominate [vt, vi] to be more powerful, important or noticeable than others The Italian team dominated through the second half of the game. She always trends to dominte the conversation. [vt] (used about a building or place) to be much higher than everythings else The landmark building dominate the area for miles around. chivalry [n] polite and kind behavior by men which respect towards women. currency [C, U] the</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>每日英语学习20200816</title>
      <link>https://yuallon.github.io/post/%E6%AF%8F%E6%97%A5%E8%8B%B1%E8%AF%AD%E5%AD%A6%E4%B9%A020200816/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 16 Aug 2020 23:11:23 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://yuallon.github.io/post/%E6%AF%8F%E6%97%A5%E8%8B%B1%E8%AF%AD%E5%AD%A6%E4%B9%A020200816/</guid>
      <description>Words accusation [n.] a statement saying that sb has done sth wrong excellent [adj] very good; of high quality He speaks excellent English. gulp [v] to swallow large amounts of food, drink, etc quickly glup sth (down) &amp;ndash; He gulped down his breakfast and went out. glup (for) sth &amp;ndash; She finally come to the surface, desperately gluping (for) air. [n.] the action of breathing in or swallowing sth I</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>每日英语学习20200814</title>
      <link>https://yuallon.github.io/post/%E6%AF%8F%E6%97%A5%E8%8B%B1%E8%AF%AD%E5%AD%A6%E4%B9%A020200814/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Aug 2020 23:15:32 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://yuallon.github.io/post/%E6%AF%8F%E6%97%A5%E8%8B%B1%E8%AF%AD%E5%AD%A6%E4%B9%A020200814/</guid>
      <description>Study: Heatwaves Can Force Ocean Life to Flee Great Distances A new study shows that heatwaves can cause fish and other creatures in the world’s oceans to travel thousands of kilometers in search of cooler waters. Scientists at the U.S. National Oceanic and Atmospheric Administration, or NOAA, reported on the study last week. Their research is based on a new way of measuring heatwaves.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>每日英语学习20200812</title>
      <link>https://yuallon.github.io/post/%E6%AF%8F%E6%97%A5%E8%8B%B1%E8%AF%AD%E5%AD%A6%E4%B9%A020200812/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Aug 2020 23:31:58 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://yuallon.github.io/post/%E6%AF%8F%E6%97%A5%E8%8B%B1%E8%AF%AD%E5%AD%A6%E4%B9%A020200812/</guid>
      <description>Talking about Your Hometown Part One: Introducing your hometown I live in a (city/town/village). I live in a small village, but it&amp;rsquo;s a quiet place. (Add more detail, where/big or small etc) Part Two: Adding background and details Q1: What&amp;rsquo;s your hometown famous for? Q2: Can you think of some words you could use to describe your hometown? Q3: How long have you lived there? I live in Lankao, a</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to Improve Your English Writing</title>
      <link>https://yuallon.github.io/post/how-to-improve-your-english-writing/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Aug 2020 15:46:53 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://yuallon.github.io/post/how-to-improve-your-english-writing/</guid>
      <description>Part One: Understand your audience You should ask yourself some questions before you writing: Who are you writing for? friend/colleague/teacher/manager/examiner/etc? What are you trying to achieve? Give someone information? Convince somebody of your point? Entertain somebody? Give someone advice? &amp;hellip; What does your reader want? Why your reader spent his/her time to read what you have writen? Part Two: Plan your writing You&amp;rsquo;d better to list some important information before</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>每日英语学习20200806</title>
      <link>https://yuallon.github.io/post/%E6%AF%8F%E6%97%A5%E8%8B%B1%E8%AF%AD%E5%AD%A6%E4%B9%A020200806/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Aug 2020 23:07:05 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://yuallon.github.io/post/%E6%AF%8F%E6%97%A5%E8%8B%B1%E8%AF%AD%E5%AD%A6%E4%B9%A020200806/</guid>
      <description>Massive Explosion Killed More Than 70, Injured Thousands in Beirut A massive explosion shook Beirut Tuesday, flattening much of the Lebanese capital’s port and damaging buildings across the city. The country’s health minister reported more than 70 people were killed and at least 3,000 others were injured. Officials expected the number of dead to</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>每日英语学习20200805</title>
      <link>https://yuallon.github.io/post/%E6%AF%8F%E6%97%A5%E8%8B%B1%E8%AF%AD%E5%AD%A6%E4%B9%A020200805/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Aug 2020 23:15:33 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://yuallon.github.io/post/%E6%AF%8F%E6%97%A5%E8%8B%B1%E8%AF%AD%E5%AD%A6%E4%B9%A020200805/</guid>
      <description>Managing Your Work, Your Child&amp;rsquo;s Work Online The coronavirus pandemic has changed many things about everyday life. One big change is childcare – or the lack of it. As many childcare providers（育儿机构） closed as part of public safety measures, so did schools, offices and businesses. Social restrictions also tightened. This meant many older adults were unable</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>每日英语学习20200804</title>
      <link>https://yuallon.github.io/post/%E6%AF%8F%E6%97%A5%E8%8B%B1%E8%AF%AD%E5%AD%A6%E4%B9%A020200804/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 04 Aug 2020 23:00:04 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://yuallon.github.io/post/%E6%AF%8F%E6%97%A5%E8%8B%B1%E8%AF%AD%E5%AD%A6%E4%B9%A020200804/</guid>
      <description>WHO: ‘There’s No Silver Bullet’ against COVID-19 The World Health Organization, or WHO, warned on Monday that there might never be a “silver bullet” or an extraordinary（特别的） solution</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>每日英语学习20200803</title>
      <link>https://yuallon.github.io/post/%E6%AF%8F%E6%97%A5%E8%8B%B1%E8%AF%AD%E5%AD%A6%E4%B9%A020200803/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Aug 2020 21:34:10 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://yuallon.github.io/post/%E6%AF%8F%E6%97%A5%E8%8B%B1%E8%AF%AD%E5%AD%A6%E4%B9%A020200803/</guid>
      <description>Study: Plastic Pollution Flowing into Oceans to Triple by 2040 The amount of plastic waste flowing into the ocean could triple in the next 20 years unless businesses and governments act to reduce plastic production. That warning comes from a new study that appeared recently in the publication Science. The study was carried out（执行，完成） by scientists and industry experts for The</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>每日英语20200802</title>
      <link>https://yuallon.github.io/post/%E6%AF%8F%E6%97%A5%E8%8B%B1%E8%AF%AD%E5%AD%A6%E4%B9%A020200802/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 02 Aug 2020 23:12:11 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://yuallon.github.io/post/%E6%AF%8F%E6%97%A5%E8%8B%B1%E8%AF%AD%E5%AD%A6%E4%B9%A020200802/</guid>
      <description>Staying Safe During a Lightning Storm From VOA Learning English, this is the Health &amp;amp; Lifestyle Report. Lightning is one of the most powerful weather forces to hit Earth. These huge bolts of electricity that strike during storms can cause destruction and death. Lightning can heat the air around it to temperatures five times hotter than the surface of the sun. Lightning is very common. It is estimated that every</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>每日英语学习20200801</title>
      <link>https://yuallon.github.io/post/%E6%AF%8F%E6%97%A5%E8%8B%B1%E8%AF%AD%E5%AD%A6%E4%B9%A020200801/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 01 Aug 2020 20:08:56 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://yuallon.github.io/post/%E6%AF%8F%E6%97%A5%E8%8B%B1%E8%AF%AD%E5%AD%A6%E4%B9%A020200801/</guid>
      <description>The breakfast history of America Since the earliest days of the United States, Americans began their days by eating whatever was most easily availble. These foods often included breads, eggs or leftovers(复数表示剩余物，残羹剩饭；单数表示遗物，遗留) &amp;ndash; food left ove</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>每日英语学习20200730</title>
      <link>https://yuallon.github.io/post/%E6%AF%8F%E6%97%A5%E8%8B%B1%E8%AF%AD%E5%AD%A6%E4%B9%A020200730/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Jul 2020 22:32:09 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://yuallon.github.io/post/%E6%AF%8F%E6%97%A5%E8%8B%B1%E8%AF%AD%E5%AD%A6%E4%B9%A020200730/</guid>
      <description>When you feel depressed, you can hold a tree! To stay safe during the corovirus pandemic, we have had to sacrifice（牺牲） many things we enjoy, including physical contact with others. Gone are handshakes, kisses and hugs. Research has shown that humans need physical touch to stay mentally and physically healthy. Without it, many become lonely, sad and even</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>英文中时钟的读法</title>
      <link>https://yuallon.github.io/post/%E8%8B%B1%E6%96%87%E4%B8%AD%E6%97%B6%E9%92%9F%E7%9A%84%E8%AF%BB%E6%B3%95/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Jul 2020 14:38:46 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://yuallon.github.io/post/%E8%8B%B1%E6%96%87%E4%B8%AD%E6%97%B6%E9%92%9F%E7%9A%84%E8%AF%BB%E6%B3%95/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>英语中介词on in At在时间中的用法</title>
      <link>https://yuallon.github.io/post/%E8%8B%B1%E8%AF%AD%E4%B8%AD%E4%BB%8B%E8%AF%8Don-in-at%E5%9C%A8%E6%97%B6%E9%97%B4%E4%B8%AD%E7%9A%84%E7%94%A8%E6%B3%95/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Jul 2020 18:13:44 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://yuallon.github.io/post/%E8%8B%B1%E8%AF%AD%E4%B8%AD%E4%BB%8B%E8%AF%8Don-in-at%E5%9C%A8%E6%97%B6%E9%97%B4%E4%B8%AD%E7%9A%84%E7%94%A8%E6%B3%95/</guid>
      <description>at：表示某一特定时间 At night At 10:30 am At afternoon At the moment on：表示日期 On 6 March On New Year&amp;rsquo;s Eve On my birthday in：表示月、年、世纪和更长的时间段 In the morning/evening In May (month) In summer (season) In 1990 (year) In the</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Eleven Ways the Little Prince Prepared Us for Adulthood</title>
      <link>https://yuallon.github.io/post/eleven-ways-the-little-prince-prepared-us-for-adulthood/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 19 Jul 2020 23:05:30 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://yuallon.github.io/post/eleven-ways-the-little-prince-prepared-us-for-adulthood/</guid>
      <description>[Forward] How &amp;lsquo;The Little Prince&amp;rsquo; Prepped Us For Adulthood By Bustle To a child, the grown-up world can be perplexing. What is this &amp;ldquo;work&amp;rdquo; they always claim to have? Why do they refuse to run around in fields and find shapes in clouds? And why do they assume that children know nothing? Anyone who remembers her child self will probably remember being completely confused by this adult world that seemed</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Talk About Food</title>
      <link>https://yuallon.github.io/post/talk-about-food/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Jul 2020 22:34:59 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://yuallon.github.io/post/talk-about-food/</guid>
      <description>When we meet a foreigner or have a break in an international conference, what&amp;rsquo;s the best way to star conversation topics? According to research, food is one of the most common topics people talk about while on break. ###Why is talking about food such a great idea? People like food. Thinking about food, thinking about dessert or main dished. Food can bring people together. At work, we often have barbecues</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to Express Rain in English</title>
      <link>https://yuallon.github.io/post/how-to-express-rain-in-english/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 Jul 2020 17:07:40 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://yuallon.github.io/post/how-to-express-rain-in-english/</guid>
      <description>drizzle or sprink n. very little rain; stronger than mist, but less than a shower. v. rain lightly It&amp;rsquo;s drizzling now. When it drizzles in summer, hiking can be pleasant. shower n. a sudden rain thundershower/meteor shower 雷阵雨/流星雨 He is so afraid of thundershower. pour n. rain heavily dounpour 倾盆大雨 When it rains, it pours. /习语：祸不</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Going to the PHARMACY</title>
      <link>https://yuallon.github.io/post/going-to-the-pharmacy/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Jul 2020 22:30:43 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://yuallon.github.io/post/going-to-the-pharmacy/</guid>
      <description>If we go to a pharmacy, what should we pay attention to? A pharmacy is a place where you can get medication or medicine. Another word for pharmacy is drugstore. medicine/drugs prescription drugs: you need a doctor to say, &amp;ldquo;Take this&amp;rdquo; Over the counter drugs: you do not need a prescription people in pharmacy pharmacist: a person who work at the pharmacy. they are an expert in medication. clerk/ pharmacy</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to Cancle Plans in English</title>
      <link>https://yuallon.github.io/post/how-to-cancle-plans-in-english/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Jul 2020 19:55:02 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://yuallon.github.io/post/how-to-cancle-plans-in-english/</guid>
      <description>Sometimes, we have to cancel our plans with someone due to something unexpected. Maybe we are sick. Maybe we have to go to work. When we have to cancel plans, it&amp;rsquo;s important to know how to do it in a polite that does not hurt the feelings or offend the feelings of other people. ###Here list 5 easy steps First, ask &amp;ldquo;How are you doing?&amp;quot;,when you meet your friend or</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Smartphone generation Should Wait for the Elderly to Catch Up</title>
      <link>https://yuallon.github.io/post/smartphone-generation-should-wait-for-the-elderly-to-catch-up/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Jul 2020 22:01:44 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://yuallon.github.io/post/smartphone-generation-should-wait-for-the-elderly-to-catch-up/</guid>
      <description>The technology development and aging. This is a good topic. According to the National Bureau of Statistics, the number of people aged 60 and above was 253.88 million in 2019, that is 18.1 percent of China&amp;rsquo;s population. But only 23 percent of the senior citizens were able to access the internet. With the advent of online payment, which greatly makes our lives easier. Wherever we go, we can make payment</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What Can I Hold You With</title>
      <link>https://yuallon.github.io/post/what-can-i-hold-you-with/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Jun 2020 22:53:32 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://yuallon.github.io/post/what-can-i-hold-you-with/</guid>
      <description>Today, I want to share one of my favorite English poems. It&amp;rsquo;s about love, deep love. It&amp;rsquo;s hard to find someone who understand me. If I love a girl, I hope she can accept my good side and bad side. I can give her all my things. Would you like listen my story? What Can I Hold You With? I offer you lean streets, desperate sunsets, the moon of the</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>War Poverty and Pandemic</title>
      <link>https://yuallon.github.io/post/warpovertypandemic/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Jun 2020 16:46:08 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://yuallon.github.io/post/warpovertypandemic/</guid>
      <description>Today, I want to share a cartoon drawing a family flee their home owing to the war and meet the pandemic. The story is compact but make me ponder. I will slice the picture into many parts and translate the words into Chinese. War, Poverty and Pandemic Families flee their homes to save their lives but they can&amp;rsquo;t outrun the coronavirus. By Heather Murdock and Brian Williamson | VOA News</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>每日英语06 22 2020</title>
      <link>https://yuallon.github.io/post/%E6%AF%8F%E6%97%A5%E8%8B%B1%E8%AF%AD06-22-2020/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Jun 2020 23:29:21 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://yuallon.github.io/post/%E6%AF%8F%E6%97%A5%E8%8B%B1%E8%AF%AD06-22-2020/</guid>
      <description>Seven steps can stop bad information We want to help our family and friends when we read some information going viral on the internet, especially COVID-19. Here are some advice to help us avoid the fishy site. 1 Stop and think One thing you can do to halt misinformation is to simply stop and think. If you have any doubts, pause, and check it out further. 2 Check your source</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>英语国际音标</title>
      <link>https://yuallon.github.io/post/%E8%8B%B1%E8%AF%AD%E5%9B%BD%E9%99%85%E9%9F%B3%E6%A0%87/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Jun 2020 22:59:54 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://yuallon.github.io/post/%E8%8B%B1%E8%AF%AD%E5%9B%BD%E9%99%85%E9%9F%B3%E6%A0%87/</guid>
      <description>###英语48个国际音标 元音 or 辅音 音标 单元音 /i:/ /ɪ/ /e/ /æ/ /ɜ:/ /ə/, /ɑ:/ /ʌ/ /ɔ:/ /ɒ/ /u:/ /ʊ/ 双元音 /aɪ/ /eɪ/ /aʊ</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>