<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>英文 on 愿我如星君如月，夜夜流光相皎洁！</title>
    <link>https://yuallon.github.io/categories/%E8%8B%B1%E6%96%87/</link>
    <description>Recent content in 英文 on 愿我如星君如月，夜夜流光相皎洁！</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 02 Jul 2020 19:55:02 +0800</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://yuallon.github.io/categories/%E8%8B%B1%E6%96%87/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>How to Cancle Plans in English</title>
      <link>https://yuallon.github.io/post/how-to-cancle-plans-in-english/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Jul 2020 19:55:02 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://yuallon.github.io/post/how-to-cancle-plans-in-english/</guid>
      <description>Sometimes, we have to cancel our plans with someone due to something unexpected. Maybe we are sick. Maybe we have to go to work. When we have to cancel plans, it&amp;rsquo;s important to know how to do it in a polite that does not hurt the feelings or offend the feelings of other people. ###Here list 5 easy steps First, ask &amp;ldquo;How are you doing?&amp;quot;,when you meet your friend or</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Smartphone generation Should Wait for the Elderly to Catch Up</title>
      <link>https://yuallon.github.io/post/smartphone-generation-should-wait-for-the-elderly-to-catch-up/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Jul 2020 22:01:44 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://yuallon.github.io/post/smartphone-generation-should-wait-for-the-elderly-to-catch-up/</guid>
      <description>The technology development and aging. This is a good topic. According to the National Bureau of Statistics, the number of people aged 60 and above was 253.88 million in 2019, that is 18.1 percent of China&amp;rsquo;s population. But only 23 percent of the senior citizens were able to access the internet. With the advent of online payment, which greatly makes our lives easier. Wherever we go, we can make payment</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What Can I Hold You With</title>
      <link>https://yuallon.github.io/post/what-can-i-hold-you-with/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Jun 2020 22:53:32 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://yuallon.github.io/post/what-can-i-hold-you-with/</guid>
      <description>Today, I want to share one of my favorite English poems. It&amp;rsquo;s about love, deep love. It&amp;rsquo;s hard to find someone who understand me. If I love a girl, I hope she can accept my good side and bad side. I can give her all my things. Would you like listen my story? What Can I Hold You With? I offer you lean streets, desperate sunsets, the moon of the</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>War Poverty and Pandemic</title>
      <link>https://yuallon.github.io/post/warpovertypandemic/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Jun 2020 16:46:08 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://yuallon.github.io/post/warpovertypandemic/</guid>
      <description>Today, I want to share a cartoon drawing a family flee their home owing to the war and meet the pandemic. The story is compact but make me ponder. I will slice the picture into many parts and translate the words into Chinese. War, Poverty and Pandemic Families flee their homes to save their lives but they can&amp;rsquo;t outrun the coronavirus. By Heather Murdock and Brian Williamson | VOA News</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>每日英语06 22 2020</title>
      <link>https://yuallon.github.io/post/%E6%AF%8F%E6%97%A5%E8%8B%B1%E8%AF%AD06-22-2020/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Jun 2020 23:29:21 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://yuallon.github.io/post/%E6%AF%8F%E6%97%A5%E8%8B%B1%E8%AF%AD06-22-2020/</guid>
      <description>Seven steps can stop bad information We want to help our family and friends when we read some information going viral on the internet, especially COVID-19. Here are some advice to help us avoid the fishy site. 1 Stop and think One thing you can do to halt misinformation is to simply stop and think. If you have any doubts, pause, and check it out further. 2 Check your source</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>英语国际音标</title>
      <link>https://yuallon.github.io/post/%E8%8B%B1%E8%AF%AD%E5%9B%BD%E9%99%85%E9%9F%B3%E6%A0%87/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Jun 2020 22:59:54 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://yuallon.github.io/post/%E8%8B%B1%E8%AF%AD%E5%9B%BD%E9%99%85%E9%9F%B3%E6%A0%87/</guid>
      <description>###英语48个国际音标 元音 or 辅音 音标 单元音 /i:/ /ɪ/ /e/ /æ/ /ɜ:/ /ə/, /ɑ:/ /ʌ/ /ɔ:/ /ɒ/ /u:/ /ʊ/ 双元音 /aɪ/ /eɪ/ /aʊ</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>